- [Instructor] Okay, so finally but not least,
we need to add the endpoint
that will allow us to delete any players.
So again, we're going to start with the controller
and we're going to create a brand new controller
that will be called deletePlayer,
and we're going to make this function async,
request, response.
And let's do the function here.
We're going to try again,
and then as before, we're going to copy the catch,
send the error if there's an error,
and then here we're going to await Player,
and the function we're going to use is deleteOne.
We need to pass some parameters here.
So we need to pass an ID
and it's going to be what we have
in the prompts of the requests,
and we're going to be calling this PlayerID like so.
And that's basically the function that will delete one,
but then we don't have a response
because we don't have anything to send back,
so we need to send something different.
So in this case,
what we're going to do is send a message instead.
So we're going to create a JSON message
that will be as such.
Successfully deleted player.
And that's pretty much what we need.
We don't need to send anything else,
and that's the controller for you.
And then like before,
and again, if you feel like you get the gist of it now,
you can go ahead and pause the video and do it yourself,
but for everybody else, we need to have a delete endpoint,
and you want to make sure you first pass the controller here
'cause we're going to need it,
and the lead endpoint, and pass the deletePlayer.
And again, why we're using this
is because we need the player ID.
We need to know exactly which one we're deleting.
And so we need this endpoint to pass the ID of the player,
use this controller and this method
to delete a specific player.
And that's pretty much what we need.
So save this.
Make sure your server's running and there's no errors,
'cause it happens to all of us.
If there's an error here, you may have a typo,
you may have done something completely different
from what I've done,
or sometimes the version of the frameworks
that we're using in this course
are a bit behind what you're using.
It may have some things that are not working the same way.
If you're getting any messages,
my advice to you is always to Google it
to make sure that you understand what is the error
if you don't understand it,
and then fix it based on documentation.
So that's always my recommendation.
It happens to all of us.
It happens to me, too,
when I build applications for the companies that I work for.
Alright, so let's move on to test this.
So let's go to our database,
and let's run it here
just to make sure I have the latest and the greatest.
So I'm going to delete this one here.
So copy, value is text.
I'm going to delete this one and then we'll check back,
and I'm going to go in Postman.
And in this one, you don't need to send anything in the body
so I'm going to remove these and select the delete method.
Make sure I'm pasting the exact ID that I want to delete.
This is the endpoint.
So I'm going to send this
and the message that I get back
is, "Successfully deleted player."
And if you want to be absolutely sure,
but you would get in there if it didn't work,
you could go back to the source of the data
and you'll see that this particular ID
will be gone once I run query again in Mongo.
And again, you see that it worked.
Okay, so that completes our backend.
We're going to be moving to the front end, which is exciting,
in the next video.